A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, RG 2 FA433
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office of the Messieurs Rockefeller (OMR) Files, 1878-1972; bulk; 2; 21 Cubic Feet
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1914-1961 (bulk 1947-1961); bulk; 4; 15 box(es)
    - Memorial Hospital - Expansion Program - General, 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 433)
      MSKCC Master Plan for Physical Expansion (May 1960); Comprehensive Master Plan for Development and Modernization of the Physical Facilities of the MSKCC (November 30, 1961).
    - Memorial Hospital - Expansion Program - 345 East 68th Street (New York City) - General, 1949, 1954, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 434)
      See also Normandy Realty Company.
      Memorandum on use of space for staff housing (1949); Rehabilitation Program (1954).
    - Memorial Hospital - Expansion Program - 345 East 68th Street - Tenant Relocation Bureau, Inc., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 435)
      Memorandum of suggested Procedure in Connection with Removing Remaining Tenants in Apartment House
    - Memorial Hospital - Finances, 1948-1953 (Box 33, Folder 436)
    - Memorial Hospital - Finances, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 437)
    - Memorial Hospital - Finances, 1959-1962 (Box 33, Folder 438)
    - Memorial Hospital - Firestone, Russell A., Memorial Fund, 1951-1956 (Box 33, Folder 439)
      For support of Department of Radiation Therapy
    - Memorial Hospital - Fund Raising - General, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 440)
    - Memorial Hospital - Fund Raising - General, 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 441)
      Men's and women's committees; discussions of tobacco industry; Alfred P. Sloan, Jr., Observations on fund raising [August 1953?].
    - Memorial Hospital - Fund Raising - General, 1954-1958 (Box 33, Folder 442)
    - Memorial Hospital - Fund Raising - General, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 444)
      1960 materials charged out from files.
    - Memorial Hospital - Fund Raising - Five Year Development Program, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 445)
      Plan and Organization of Five-Year Build-UP Program, by C.E.Cameron, August 15, 1957.
    - Memorial Hospital - Fund Raising - Five Year Development Program, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 446)
      75th Anniversary Fund; MSKCC Acceleration Program [1961].
    - Memorial Hospital - Giffis, Stanton, Fund, 1951-1961 (Box 34, Folder 447)
      Contributions funded maintenance of Camp Uncas and joint facilities for Cornell New York Hospital and Memorial Center.
    - Memorial Hospital - Kerbs Memorial Hall, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 448)
      Gift of Jeanne E. Kerbs. Dedication December 23, 1952.
    - Memorial Hospital - Kerbs Memorial Hall, 1953-1956 (Box 34, Folder 449)
      LSR address at unveiling of portraits of Edward A. and Alice H. Kerbs, April 1956.
    - Memorial Hospital - Letters of Appreciation, 1951-1955 (Box 34, Folder 450)
    - Memorial Hospital - Medical Staff Fund, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 451)
    - Memorial Hospital - Metcalf-Hatch Bill and New York State Society for Medical Research, 1951-1954 (Box 34, Folder 452)
      Use of strays and pound animals in laboratory research.
    - Memorial Hospital - Meyer Physiology Laboratory and Betatron Unit, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 453)
    - Memorial Hospital - Meyer Physiology Laboratory and Betatron Unit, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 454)
      Dedication of Physiology Laboratory and Kress Betatron unit, October 14, 1952.
    - Memorial Hospital - Meyer Physiology Laboratory and Betatron Unit, 1953-1956, 1959-1961 (Box 34, Folder 455)
    - Memorial Hospital - Murray, Albert, Paintings, 1951-1954, 1959; Still Images: 2 black-and-white prints (6.75" x 9.75"). (Box 34, Folder 456)
      Portraits of Reginald Coombe, Alfred P. Sloan, Elise Strang L'Esperance, C.P. Rhoads. Includes photos of Sloan portrait (1951).
      See also Memorial Hospital - Staff (Alphabetical) - Rhoads, C.P., 1950-1960, for letter from Murray to LSR, September 5, 1956, concerning portrait of LSR.
    - Memorial Hospital - Officers and Trustees, 1950-1961 (Box 34, Folder 457)
      Lists of officers and committee memberships
    - Memorial Hospital - Organization - Correspondence, 1950-1952 May (Box 34, Folder 458)
      Frederick Kilduff financial and administrative review; Alfred P. Sloan, LSR, Frank Howard, and Ogden White correspondence on reorganization of fundraising and C.P. Rhoads' administrative and research roles.
    - Memorial Hospital - Organization - Correspondence, 1952 July - December (Box 34, Folder 459)
      Cresap, McCormick and Paget study
    - Memorial Hospital - Organization - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 460)
    - Memorial Hospital - Organization - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 34, Folder 461)
      Henry T. Randall report on staff reorganization, September 1955.
    - Memorial Hospital - Organization - Survey Report, 1953 March 13 (Box 35, Folder 462)
      Cresap, McCormick and Paget, "Organization and Control."
      Volume 1
    - Memorial Hospital - Organization - Survey Report, 1953 March 13 (Box 35, Folder 463)
      Volume 2 (Chapters 1-4)
    - Memorial Hospital - Organization - Survey Report, 1953 March 13 (Box 35, Folder 464)
      Volume 2 (Chapters 5-13)
    - Memorial Hospital - Organization - Survey Report, 1953 March 13 (Box 35, Folder 465)
      Volume 2 (Appendices)
    - Memorial Hospital - Publicity, 1949-1953 (Box 35, Folder 466)
      Press releases and clippings. Press release on leukemia treatment, April 1953.
    - Memorial Hospital - Publicity, 1954-1961 (Box 35, Folder 467)
      New York World - Telegram series, "Center of Hope: Memorial vs. Cancer," November 1960. Fourfront (MSKCC newsletter), December 1958 - October 1961.
    - Memorial Hospital - Publicity (Oversized file), 1958-1961 (Box 53, Folder 711)
      John Ferris, ""Center of Hope: Memorial vs. Cancer,"" 1960; Fourfront, 1958-1961
    - Memorial Hospital - Radio Broadcast (with Eleanor Roosevelt), 1950-1951 (Box 35, Folder 468)
      Recorded interview on WNBC (New York), January 30, 1951, with C.P. Rhoads and LSR
    - Memorial Hospital - Rogers and Butler (Architects), 1952-1955, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 469)
      Renovation of staff facilities; block plan study, York Avenue and 68th-69th Streets; Bio-Physics building on 68th Street
    - Memorial Hospital - Saranac Lake, 1952-1961 (Box 35, Folder 470)
      Camp Nepahwin title transferred to Memorial Center, February 1953.
    - Memorial Hospital - Saranac Lake, 1952-1961 (Box 35, Folder 470 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary Celebration, 1958-1960 (Box 35, Folder 471)
      Scientific symposium and dinner, October 20-21, 1959. Public Dinner, Waldorf Astoria, April 20, 1060.
    - Memorial Hospital - Space Planning Survey (Edwin Salmon), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 472)
      Front of File Material.
    - Memorial Hospital - Space Planning Survey (Edwin Salmon), 1956-1957 (Drawer E11, Drawer 56, Box 36, Folder 473)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1949-1950 (Box 36, Folder 474)
      Stained glass window in memory of Elizabeth H. Cullum; recruitment of nurses aides
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1949-1950 (Box 36, Folder 474 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 475)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 476)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 476 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1953 February - June (Box 36, Folder 477)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1953 July - October (Box 36, Folder 478)
      Memorandum on Harvard Plan (salary cap and pooled earnings to fund teaching and research)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 479)
      Winslow Carlton report on costs of full-time program for clinical staff; staff morale; teaching budget
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 479 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1955 January - April (Box 36, Folder 480)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1955 May - 1956 (Box 36, Folder 481)
      Henry T. Randall correspondence on Memorial Center appointments
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1955 May - 1956 (Box 36, Folder 481 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 482)
      Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. Loan Fund for Memorial residents and students; Hayes Martin retirement; Pension Committee report and plan.
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 482 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1958-1961 (Box 36, Folder 483)
      Henry T. Randall, discussions of reorganization and administration, 1950-1960.
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - General, 1958-1961 (Box 36, Folder 483 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff (Alphabetical) - Heller, John R., 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 484)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff (Alphabetical) - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr., 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 485)
      President and director of SKI, 1960
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff (Alphabetical) - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr., 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 485 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff (Alphabetical) - Rhoads, C.P., 1950-1960 (Box 36, Folder 486)
      Obituary and tributes, 1959. Includes letter from Albert Murray to LSR, September 5, 1956.
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff (Alphabetical) - Rhoads, C.P., 1950-1960 (Box 36, Folder 486 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - General, 1949-1954 (Box 37, Folder 487)
      Proposed nurses' residence and efforts to acquire property for it.
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - General, 1949-1954 (Box 37, Folder 487 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - General, 1955-1956 (Box 37, Folder 488)
      Proposed nurses' residence and efforts to acquire property for it. Includes Robert Moses, Citizens Housing and Planning Council.
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - General, 1955-1956 (Box 37, Folder 488 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - General, 1957-1958 (Box 37, Folder 489)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - General, 1957-1958 (Box 37, Folder 489 A)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - General, 1959-1961 (Box 37, Folder 490)
      Nurses' residence
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - Sloan Contribution, 1957-1961 (Box 37, Folder 491)
      Alfred P. SLoan, Jr., pledge of $4 million for nurses' residence
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - Winston Building, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 492)
      Doctors' apartments, East 67th Street
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Housing - York Avenue Redevelopment Plan, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 493)
      Plan sponsored by Memorial Center, Sloan-Kettering Institute, and Rockefeller Institute
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Professional Policy, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 494)
      Memorial Plan and limitations on professional salaries
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Professional Policy, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 495)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Professional Policy, 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 496)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Salaries, 1951-1961 (Box 37, Folder 497)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Salaries, 1951-1961 (Box 37, Folder 497 A)
      Restricted - Personnel information (salaries).
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Suggestions and Applications, 1948-1951 (Box 37, Folder 498)
    - Memorial Hospital - Staff - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 499)
    - Memorial Hospital - Taxation, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 500)
    - Memorial Hospital - Tower Clinic and Dedication, 1951-1952 (Box 38, Folder 501)
      Dedication of Clinics for Ambulatory Patients; alterations to Head and Neck Clinic.
    - Memorial Hospital - Treatment, 1950-1952 (Box 38, Folder 502)
    - Memorial Hospital - Treatment, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 503)
    - Memorial Hospital - Treatment, 1955-1956 (Box 38, Folder 504)
    - Memorial Hospital - Treatment, 1957-1961 (Box 38, Folder 505)
    - Memorial Hospital - Trusts, 1959-1961 (Box 38, Folder 506)
      Fred W. Stewart Trust Agreement
    - Memorial Hospital - United Hospital Fund Participation, 1950-1958 (Box 38, Folder 507)
    - Memorial Hospital - Volunteer Department, 1950-1961 (Box 38, Folder 508)
      Annual and a few monthly reports; recognition of indiviudals; group affiliates
    - Memorial Hospital: Bequests; Rogers Butler; Staff Housing (Oversized file), 1953, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 710)
      Schedule of wills and trusts with a Memorial interest, 1953; Plot Plan, Hospital Area, 60th-72nd Streets, 1961; Plot Plan, General Area, East 68th Street and York Avenue, 1961
    - Normandy Realty Company - General, 1950-1954 (Box 38, Folder 509)
    - Normandy Realty Company - Ogden White Files, 1950-1953 (Box 38, Folder 510)
    - Normandy Realty Company - Ogden White files (oversized material), 1951 (Box 53, Folder 712)
      Douglas Gibbons and Co., Inc.. Monthly rent statement, 1951 December
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1947-1950 (Box 39, Folder 511)
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1951-1952 (Box 39, Folder 512)
      Proposed film on cancer research; memorandum on National cancer Chemotherapy Program, March 1952; description of functions of divisions and sections of SKI Cancer Research Program, June 1952; administrative status of physiology laboratory.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1953-1954 (Box 39, Folder 513)
      Charles Kettering portrait; Memorial Center teaching program; C.P. Rhoads memorandum on relation of smoking to lung cancer, December 1953; Rhoads correspondence on relation of cancer research to treatment of mental disease and population control, June 1954.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 514)
      Proposed Biophysics facility; SKI 10th anniversary; Dr. Adam Kobryner; Warren Weaver on SKI scientific program, June 23, 1955.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 515)
      Robert H. Gregory study of SKI management and finances; research on "safe" cigarette, pituitary funciton; Carl Cameron.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1957 January - June (Box 39, Folder 516)
      Contraceptive research; Warren Weaver program review and memoranda on scope and size of SKI, April-May 1957; C. M. Mottley memorandum on space situation at SKI
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1957 October - 1958 (Box 39, Folder 517)
      Organization chart, October 1957; F.C. Redlich proposal for schizophrenia research institue; memorandum on biochemical aspects of mental disease; A. G. Bearn, "Chemistry of Heredity Disease."
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 518)
      Cancer control in Latin America; Arthur Jones and proposed psychiatric research institute (H. W Kruse, Lawrence Kubie, Alfred P. Sloan), 1957-1959.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - General, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 519)
      African Research Foundation; Alfred P. Sloan Cancer Research Awards; Souther Research Institute (Kettering-Meyer Laboratory), 1953-1961; board organization.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - By-laws and Incorporation, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 520)
      Frank Howard and incorporation and operating agreements, by-laws.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - By-laws and Incorporation, 1954-1959 (Box 39, Folder 521)
      Alfred P. Sloan, Jr., and organization amendments
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Cornell University, 1948-1949 (Box 40, Folder 522)
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Cornell University, 1950 January-April (Box 40, Folder 523)
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Cornell University, 1950 May - October (Box 40, Folder 524)
      Agreement for coordinated program of teaching and research, June 20, 1950.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Cornell University, 1951-1959 (Box 40, Folder 525)
      Memorandum on proposed biophysical research facility, 1955.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Proposed New Laboratory (East 68th Street), 1956-1958, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 526)
      Includes memorandum on Patent Policy applicable to Cancer Chemotherapy Industrial Research Contracts, United States Public Health Service, July 1958
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Publicity, 1955-1960 (Box 40, Folder 527)
      Memoranda on conditions for publishing medical research; Frank Howard memorandum on Cancer Chemotherapy, August 1956; Kettering Digest, August 1956.
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Scientific Policy Committee Meetings, 1956-1957, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 528)
      Includes Warren Weaver's program review, April 12, 1957
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Walker Laboratory (Rye, New York), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 529)
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Walker Laboratory (Rye, New York), 1958-1961; Still Image: color 8.5" x 11" glossy print. (Box 40, Folder 530)
      Includes color image of Walker Laboratory, from "Final Report on Walker Laboratory Project," June 2, 1959.
    - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - General, 1948-1954 (Box 40, Folder 531)
    - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - General, 1955-1961 (Box 40, Folder 532)
    - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - By-Laws, 1950-1952 (Box 40, Folder 533)
    - Strang Cancer Prevention Center, 1950-1961 (Box 40, Folder 534)
  - Financial Materials, 1912-1961; 5; 9 box(es)
    Other files relating to the brokerage business are found in the Personal Papers series, under New York Stock Exchange Seat. Records of LSR's Contributions are found in the Personal Papers series.
    Series 5 Financial Materials is restricted from scholarly access until 2030.
    Files in the Financial Materials series are grouped into categories of general finances, brokerage business, children, or personal.
    The general Finances files include correspondence concerning gifts, personal expenses, LSR's loan account with Jesup and Lamont, and articles, press releases, and memoranda on venture capital opportunities and investments. Personal files contain records relating to LSR's household and investment accounts, annual financial statements, securities holdings, loans made to individuals, and trust accounts. The Brokerage Business files contain income statements from LSR's stock exchange "business" from 1937-1941. Most of the financial and investment records in this series cover only the period up to the early 1940s.
    - General - Finances, 1912-1939 (Box 41, Folder 535)
      Restricted from scholarly access until 2030.
    - General - Finances, 1946-1961 (Box 41, Folder 536)
      Includes memo on Public Financing of Resort and Development Investments by R. G. Coombe
    - Brokerage Business - Chase Bank - Business Account, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 537)
    - Brokerage Business - New York Stock Exchange Seat - Business Income (Statements), 1937-1941 (Box 41, Folder 538)
    - Children - Gifts to Children, 1948-1952 (Box 41, Folder 539)
    - Children - Investments and Accounts, 1940-1948, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 540)
    - Children - Trusts - General, 1944-1959 (Box 41, Folder 541)
    - Children - Trusts - Rockefeller, Laura Spelman - General, 1941-1948, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 542)
    - Children - Trusts - Rockefeller, Laura Spelman - Trust Indenture, 1936-1938, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 543)
    - Children - Trusts - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1944-1948, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 544)
    - Children - Trusts - Rockefeller, Lucy Aldrich - General, 1941-1948, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 545)
    - Children - Trusts - Rockefeller, Lucy Aldrich - Trust Indenture, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 546)
    - Children - Trusts - Rockefeller, Marion French - General, 1941-1948, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 547)
    - Children - Trusts - Rockefeller, Marion French - Trust Indenture, 1938, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 548)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - General, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 549)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 January 1-9 (Box 42, Folder 550)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 January 15-31 (Box 42, Folder 551)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 February 1-7 (Box 42, Folder 552)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 February 13-29 (Box 42, Folder 553)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 March 1-12 (Box 42, Folder 554)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 March 15-30 (Box 42, Folder 555)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 April 1-4 (Box 42, Folder 556)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 April 15-30 (Box 42, Folder 557)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 May 1-7 (Box 42, Folder 558)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 May 14-31 (Box 42, Folder 559)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 June 1-12 (Box 42, Folder 560)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 June 13-21 (Box 42, Folder 561)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 July 1-3 (Box 43, Folder 562)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 July 9-30 (Box 43, Folder 563)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 August (Box 43, Folder 564)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 September 1-5 (Box 43, Folder 565)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 September 9-30 (Box 43, Folder 566)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 October (Box 43, Folder 567)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 November 1-7 (Box 43, Folder 568)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 November 13-29 (Box 43, Folder 569)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 December 5-9 (Box 43, Folder 570)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1940 December 10-31 (Box 43, Folder 571)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 January 2-9 (Box 44, Folder 572)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 January 13-31 (Box 44, Folder 573)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 February 1-6 (Box 44, Folder 574)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 February 7-28 (Box 44, Folder 575)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 March 1-5 (Box 44, Folder 576)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 March 6-31 (Box 44, Folder 577)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 April 1-3 (Box 44, Folder 578)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 April 8-30 (Box 44, Folder 579)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 May 1-6 (Box 44, Folder 580)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 May 7-29 (Box 44, Folder 581)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 June 1-9 (Box 44, Folder 582)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 June 11-28 (Box 44, Folder 583)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 July (Box 45, Folder 584)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 August 1-7 (Box 45, Folder 585)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 August 13-29 (Box 45, Folder 586)
    - Personal - Chase Bank - Household Account - Bills Paid, 1941 September 4-9 (Box 45, Folder 587)